// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "FIND VERB: Meera sings song.",
    answer: "Sings",
    options: [
      "Meera",
      "Sings",
      "Song",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "We painted room blue.",
    answer: "Painted",
    options: [
      "Painted",
      "We",
      "Room",
      "Blue"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "He paid for the bread.",
    answer: "Paid",
    options: [
      "Bread",
      "For",
      "Paid",
      "He"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Sai played outside.",
    answer: "Played",
    options: [
      "Sue",
      "Played",
      "Outside",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "We went to the Library. ",
    answer: "Went",
    options: [
      "Went",
      "Library",
      "We",
      "To"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "The Musician beats his drums .",
    answer: "Beats",
    options: [
      "Musician",
      "His",
      "Beats",
      "The"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "Arun goes to school",
    answer: "Goes",
    options: [
      "School",
      "Arun",
      "To",
      "Goes"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "The snail slowly crawed.",
    answer: "Crawed",
    options: [
      "Snail",
      "Slowly",
      "Crawed",
      "The"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "The teacher read the book out loud. ",
    answer: "Read",
    options: [
      "Read",
      "Book",
      "Loud",
      "The"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "The children ran away ",
    answer: "Ran",
    options: [
      "Away",
      "Children",
      "The",
      "Ran"
    ]
  }, 
];